Guide to the Wesley C. Salmon Papers, 1950-2003 ASP.2003.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Correspondence, 1960-2010; 1963-2001; I.
  - Correspondents - M, 11.
    - Marmet, Paul, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Marshall, Catherine, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Marshall, Christopher, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Marshall, Rebecca, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Marsonet, Michele, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Martin, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Martin, Ed, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Martin, Michael, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Martin, Norman, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Martin, Ray, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Martin, Tom, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Marvin, Edwin, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Marx, Melvin, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Mary, 1969-1973 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Masani, Pesi, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Mason, Homer, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Massey, Gerald, 1969-1997 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Mathers, Robert, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Matthen, Mohan, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Matthews, Michael, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Mavrodes, George, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Maxwell, Grover, 1966-1981 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Maxwell, Nick, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Mayo, Deborah, 1987-1999 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Mays, Wolfe, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - McCae, Jim, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - McCaleb, Claude, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - McCallum, Valerie, 1966-1974 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - McCann, Charles, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - McCartan, Patrick, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - McCarthy, Robert, undated (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - McCurdy, Chris, 1990-1994 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - McDonald, Joyce, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - McEvoy, John, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - McInerey, Peter, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - McIntyre, Lee, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - McKie, John, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - McKinlay, Steve, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - McLaughlin, Robert, 1966-73 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - McMahon, William, 1980-1990 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - McMichael, Alan, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - McMillan, Evelyn, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - McMullin, Ernan, 1966-1979 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Meehl, Paul, 1979-1997 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Meisel, Sabine, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Meixner, John, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Melden, A.I., 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - Mellish, M.J., 1974 (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - Mellor, D.H., 1988 (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - Mellor, Hugh, 1974-1979 (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - Mendelssohn, Maxine, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - Menzies, Peter, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 64)
    - Merle, Elisabeth, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - Merrill, Daniel, 1966-1982 (Box 12, Folder 66)
    - Merrison, Alex, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 67)
    - Meyer, Bob, 1974-1998 (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - Michalos, Alex, 1964-1974 (Box 12, Folder 69)
    - Michelsen, John, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 70)
    - Middlemas, Michael, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 71)
    - Mihram, Danielle, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 72)
    - Mike, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 73)
    - Milford, Jerome, undated (Box 12, Folder 74)
    - Miller, Arthur, 1976-1978 (Box 12, Folder 75)
    - Miller, David, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 76)
    - Miller, George, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 77)
    - Miller, Jon, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 78)
    - Miller, Kathleen, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 79)
    - Miller, Lou, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 80)
    - Miller, Mary, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 81)
    - Mischel, Theodore, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 82)
    - Mishalani, Jim, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 83)
    - Misiek, Josef, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 84)
    - Mistry, Hema, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 85)
    - Mitchell, Sam, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 86)
    - Mitchell, Sandy, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 87)
    - Mitchell, Steven, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 88)
    - Momtchiloff, Peter, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 89)
    - Mondadori, Marco, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 90)
    - Moneysmith, Jayne, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 91)
    - Montague, Richard, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 92)
    - Montgomery, H.A., 1966 (Box 12, Folder 93)
    - Moneypenny, Phillip, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 94)
    - Moody, Ernest, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Mooney, H.A., 1998 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Moor, Jim, 1971-1975 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Moore, Asher, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Moore, Edward, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Moore, John D., 1964-1967 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Moore, Marti, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Moore, Terrence, 1990-1993 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Morgan, Greg, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 8 b)
    - Moravcsik, Julius, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Morgan, Greg, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Morgareidge, Clayton, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Morscher, Edgar, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Moser, Paul, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Mosteller, Frederick, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Moulton, E.R., 1975 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Moulton, James, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Moulton, Zjemi, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Mugnai, Massimo, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Muhlholzer, Felix, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Mullane, Harvey, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Muller, Gert, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Mulvaney, Robert, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Mundy, Brent, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Munster, Ralf, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Mura, Alberto, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Murad, Hazim, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Murphy, Jeffrie, 1973-1989 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Musgrave, John, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Myren, Richard, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Correspondents - N - O, Undated; 12.
      - NACS Cornell, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 30)
      - Nadel, Lynne, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 31)
      - Nagel, Thomas, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 32)
      - Nagley, Winfield E., 1965-1975 (Box 13, Folder 33)
      - Nagy, Paul, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 34)
      - Nair, G. Sukumaran, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 35)
      - Nakhnikian, George, 1963-1986 (Box 13, Folder 36)
      - Naylor, Andrew, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 37)
      - Neal, 1971-1976 (Box 13, Folder 38)
      - Neal, Raymond, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 39)
      - Neapolitan, Richard, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 40)
      - Neil, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 41)
      - Neilson, D. D., 1976 (Box 13, Folder 42)
      - Neiman, Alven, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 43)
      - Nelson, Alan, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 44)
      - Nelson, Everett, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 45)
      - Nelson, Gretchen, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 46)
      - Nelson, Mark, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 47)
      - Nelson, Raymond, 1967-1978 (Box 13, Folder 48)
      - Nerlich, Graham, 1980-1985 (Box 13, Folder 49)
      - Nery, Victor, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 50)
      - Nesie, Alissa, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 51)
      - Neta, Ram, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 52)
      - Nettler, Gwynn, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 53)
      - New York Review, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 54)
      - New Yorker, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 55)
      - Newcomb, Mildred, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 56)
      - Newman, Andrew, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 57)
      - Newman, David, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 58)
      - Newton, Roger, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 59)
      - Newton, Smith, W.H., 1987 (Box 13, Folder 60)
      - Nick, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 61)
      - Nickel, James, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 62)
      - Niiniluoto, Ilkka, 1978-1993 (Box 13, Folder 63)
      - Nilson, Don, 1968-1978 (Box 13, Folder 64)
      - Nissen, Lowell, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 65)
      - Nissim-Sabat, Charles, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 66)
      - Nola, Robert, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 67)
      - Nola, Robert, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 68)
      - Nollan, Richard, 1979-1982 (Box 13, Folder 69)
      - Nordenberg, Mark, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 70)
      - North Carolina State University, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 71)
      - North-Holland Publishing, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 72)
      - Norton, John, 1980-1999 (Box 13, Folder 73)
      - Nozick, Robert, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 74)
      - Nunnink, Louise, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 75)
      - Nusbaum, Linda, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 76)
      - Nute, Donald, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 77)
      - Nye, Mary Jo, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 77 b)
      - Oberdick, Hans, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 78)
      - O'Connor, Dennis, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 79)
      - O'Connor, John, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 80)
      - O'Donohue, William, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 81)
      - O'Hear, Anthony, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 82)
      - Ohlin, Peter, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 83)
      - Olin, Russell, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 84)
      - Oliver, James, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 85)
      - Olshewsley, Thomas, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 86)
      - O'Meara, Tim, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 87)
      - O'Neal, Len, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 88)
      - Onians, Susan, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 89)
      - O'Quinlivan, Annemarie, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 90)
      - Orlen, Joel, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 91)
      - Orzeck, Art, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 92)
      - Osler, Margaret, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Osier, Pam, 1983-1988 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Osler, Margaret, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Otte, Ric (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Overmann, Ronald, 1975-94 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Overmeir, Judith, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Oxford University Press, 1970-1999 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Correspondents - P-Q, 13.
    - Pagnini, Alessandro, 1990-1995 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Pallotta, Gino, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Palomar, Velia, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Paluch, Stanley, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Pam, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Panichas, George, 1989-1993 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Papineau, David, 1979-1995 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Paprzyck, Katarzyna, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Park, Seungbae, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Parrini, Paolo, 1987-2000 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Parsons, Keith, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Parsons, Terrence, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Pasch, Alan, 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Pasquinelli, Alberto, 1970-1972 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Passmore, John, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Pat, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Patrick, J., 1982 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Paul, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Paul, Robert, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Pav, Peter, 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Peacock, Harold, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Peake, Charles, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Pearce, Alison, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Pearce, David, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Pelto, Pertti, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Peltz, Richard, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Pendleton, H., 1988 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Penelhum, Terance, 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Pennock, Rob, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Pera, Marcello, 1985-1993 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Perez, Sandra, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Perkis, Donald, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Perloff, Mickey, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Perranella, John, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Perry, Bernard, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Perry, Jim, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Perry, John, 1975-1988 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Pervin, Lawrence, 1989-1992 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Peterson, June, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Peterson, Joel, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Peter, Lindley, Carl, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Philip, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Philosopher's Annual, The, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Pickin, Kim, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Pidzarko, Eugene, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Pike, Nelson, 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Pincus, Edward, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Pink, Randall, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Pinkham, Gordon, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - Pippin, Robert, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - Pitt, Joseph, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - Pittsburgh Post Gazette, The, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 5958)
    - Plantinga, Al, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 60)
    - Playboy, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 61)
    - Poindexter DeCota, Wanda, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 62)
    - Polansky, Ronald, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 63)
    - Pospesel, Howard, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 64)
    - Postbrief, Samuel, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 65)
    - Postini, Marc, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 66)
    - Potter, Karl, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 67)
    - Poulakis, John, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 68)
    - Powell, Corey, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 69)
    - Powers, Stephen, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 70)
    - Poznanski, Edward, 1966-1973 (Box 14, Folder 71)
    - Pratt, James, 1963-1964 (Box 14, Folder 72)
    - Prentice-Hall, Inc., 1965-1998 (Box 14, Folder 73)
    - Presti, Scott, undated (Box 14, Folder 74)
    - Price, Huw, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 75)
    - Princeton University Press, 1966-1982 (Box 14, Folder 76)
    - Proctor, John, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 77)
    - Prokhovnik, Simon, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 78)
    - Proudfoot, M.A., 1998 (Box 14, Folder 79)
    - Pryweller, Dale, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 80)
    - Psillos, Stathis, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 81)
    - Puccino, Carole, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 82)
    - Pyke, L.R.D., 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 83)
    - Quantum Conference, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Quevedo, Steven, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Quine, W.V., 1966-1977 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Quinn, Michael, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Quinn, Philip, 1969-1997 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Quinn, Warren, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Correspondents - R, 14.
    - Rabinovich, Hector, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Radnitzky, Gerard, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Railton, Peter, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Rajaram, N.S., 1976 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Rawls, John, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Raynor, David, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Redhead, Michael, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Regis, Edward, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Reichenbach, Hans, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Reichenbach, Maria "Mia", 1963-1995 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Reidel, A., 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Reinhardt, Howard, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Reitan, Harald, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Remak, Henry, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Renardy, Michael, 1997-1998 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Renee, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Renzong, Qiu, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Rescher, Nicholas, 1966-1997 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Resnik, Michael, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Reynolds, James, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Rettger, Matthew, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Reupke, William, 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Rhodes, Naomi, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Richard, 1981-1992 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Richman, Robert, 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Richmond, Samuel, 1971-1989 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Rick, 1982-1991 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Ricketts, Thomas, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Ricks, Theodore, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Ridgely, Brian, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Ridgeview Publishing Co., 1981-1989 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Riedel, Marcus, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Rieksts, Oskars, 1971-1987 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Ringelheim, Joan, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Ringen, Jon, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Ringer, Fritz, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Risse, Mathias, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Rivers, George, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Rizzo, Mario, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Robert, 1965-1993 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Roberts, John, undated (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Roberts, Lawrence, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Robinson, Steve, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Robison, John, 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Rod, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Rodgers, John, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Roger, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Rogers, Ben, 1965-1984 (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Rogers, Hayward, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - Rogers, Thomas, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - Rogge, Gene, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Rohatyn, Dennis, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - Rohrlich, Fritz, 1993-1997 (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - Roller, Duane, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 60)
    - Rollin, Bernard, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 61)
    - Rollins, C.D., 1965-1979 (Box 15, Folder 62)
    - Romano, Francesco, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 63)
    - Romberg, Walter, 1969-1971 (Box 15, Folder 64)
    - Ron, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 65)
    - Rosales, Alirio, 1994-1997 (Box 15, Folder 66)
    - Rosen, Deborah, 1978-1981 (Box 15, Folder 67)
    - Rosenbaum, R.A., 1964 (Box 15, Folder 68)
    - Rosenberg, Alex, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 69)
    - Rosenberg, Charles, 1980-1986 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Rosenberg, J.L., 1986 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Rosenberg, Jerome, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Rosenblatt, Paul, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Rosenburg, Jay, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Rosenkrantz, Roger, 1980-1990 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Rosenzweig, Gloria, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Rosner, Kevin, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Ross, David, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Ross, James, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Ross, Stephen, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Rothbart, Dan, 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Rothney, G.O., 1967 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Rowan, Michael, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Rowan, Robert, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Roy, Ashok, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Rozenboom, William, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Ruben, David-Hillel, 1986-1992 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Rubenstein, Farrell, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Rubinstein, rubert, 1974-1976 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Rudner, Richard, 1964-1968 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Rudolph, Nicole, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Reubenbauer, K., 1980 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Ruse, Michael, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Russell, Bertriend, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Russell, Daniel, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Ruth, undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Ryan, Vincent, 1968-1989 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Ryle, Gilbert, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Correspondents - S-T, 15.
    - Saarinen, Esa, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Sack, Susan, undated (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Salisbury, Janet, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Salthouse, W.H., 1968 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Sam, 1966-1994 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Samitca, D.C., 1985 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Sample, Janet, 1987-1998 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Sanborn, Richard, 1970-1993 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Sandborg, David, 1993-1995 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Sanders, Gerald, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Sankey, Howard, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Santas, Gerasimos, 1973-1976 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Sarell, Moshe, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Savage, Leonard "Jimmie", 1963-1975 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Savage, Wade, 1981-1987 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Savery, Charlotte, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Savitt, Steve, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Sayre, Kenneth, 1973-1981 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Sayre-McCord, Geoff, 1988-1992 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Schaefer, John, 1975-1977 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Schafer, Lothar, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Schaffner, Kenneth, 1967-1990 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Schagrin, Morton, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Scheffler, Israel, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Scheibe, Erhard, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Scheines, Richard, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - Scheurer, Paul, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - Schick, Frederic, 1966-1968 (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Schiffer, Michael, 1977-1989 (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - Schiller, Jerome, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 59)
    - Schimming, R., 1991 (Box 16, Folder 60)
    - Schlabach, Anne, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 61)
    - Schlaffer, Heinz, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 62)
    - Schlaretzki, Emil, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 63)
    - Schlaretzki, W.E., 1963-1973 (Box 16, Folder 64)
    - Schlesinger, George, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 65)
    - Schlorse, Benjamin, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 66)
    - Schmid, Gary, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 67)
    - Schmitt, Richard, undated (Box 16, Folder 68)
    - Scheewind, J.B., 1967 (Box 16, Folder 69)
    - Schneider, Howard, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 70)
    - Schrag, Calvin, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 71)
    - Schrepel, Walter, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 72)
    - Schueler, G.F., 1997 (Box 16, Folder 73)
    - Schultz, Martin "Mike", 1972-1985 (Box 16, Folder 74)
    - Schurz, Gerhard, 1986-1990 (Box 16, Folder 75)
    - Schuster, Cynthia, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 76)
    - Schwartz, Maureen, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 77)
    - Schwartz, Stephen, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 78)
    - Science Library System, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 79)
    - Scott, Jenni, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 80)
    - Scott, Mary Lu, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 81)
    - Scribner, Phillip, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 82)
    - Schriven, Michael, 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 83)
    - Seaman, David, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 84)
    - Searle, Eleanor, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 85)
    - Seeskin, Kenneth, 1981-1983 (Box 16, Folder 86)
    - Seidel, Barbara, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 87)
    - Seidenfeld, Teddy, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 88)
    - Sen, Pranab, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 89)
    - Sellars, Wilfrid, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 90)
    - Settle, Tom, 1968-1981 (Box 16, Folder 91)
    - Shaffer, Jerome, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 92)
    - Shahan, Robert, 1970-1975 (Box 16, Folder 93)
    - Shamsi, F.A., 1972-1993 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Shanfield, Stephen, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Shapere, Dudley, (National Science Foundation), 1971-1973 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Shapiro, Lionel, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Shapiro, Stewart, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Sharlow, Mark, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Shaver, Robert, undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Shaw, James, 1968-1978 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Shaw, Jeffery, 1979-1984 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Sheetman, Joseph, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Shelanski, Vivien, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Shelton, Jim, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Sher, George, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Shildneck, Paul, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Shimony, Abner, 1965-1995 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Shiner, Rodger, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Shiner, V.J., 1975 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Shiva, Vandana, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Shotwell, David, undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Shuford, Haywood, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Sibley, F.N., 1964 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Sieg, Wilfried, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Simon, Andrew, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Simon, Carol, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Sircello, Guy, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Skipper, Rob, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Sklar, Lawrence, 1974-1994 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Skyrms, Brian, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Slaght, Ralph, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Smart, Jack, 1973-1980 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Smith, Douglas, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Smith, Gene, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Smith, Jim, 1965-1972 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Smith, Joel, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Smith, John-Christian, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Smith, Kelly, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Smith, Patricia, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Smith, Quentin, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Smokler, Howard, 1964-1967 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Smullyan, Arthur, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Snapper, Ernst, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Snyder, John, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Sober, Elliott, 1984-1997 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Soble, Alan, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Earnest, Sosa, 1968-1992 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Sojka, Gary, 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Solomonoff, Ray, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Sparmann, Iris, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Sparn, Edwin, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Spearman, Lynda, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Specter, Arlen, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - Spencer-Wood, Suzanne, undated (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Spohn, Wolfgang, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - Spranzi-Zuber, Marta, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - Squires, Frederic, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - Srzednicki, Jan, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - Stachel, John, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 57)
    - State University of New York, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 58)
    - Staire, Allen, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 59)
    - Stanford, Bookstore, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 60)
    - Steel, Dan, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - Stegmuller, Wolfgang, 1970-1974 (Box 17, Folder 62)